so now let's try our hand at the mo SC
protocol suppose we have three cores
maintain moiseev coherence and the
variable X starts out by only being in
memory so it's not in any of the caches
so we have our three course C 0 C 1 and
C 2 and the first axis that happens is
read X on core 0 what is the new state
of this block in the cache that belongs
to this core next c1 does read X what is
the new state of this block on this
score and what is the state of this
block on C 0 after c1 is done with this
read now c2 does read X what is its new
state for this block and what is the new
state of this block in c1s cache or does
it just stay the same and finally see
one does a write to X what is the new
state of the Block in see once cash-in
c2s cache and in the cache of course is